James Ciclitira

Product Designer based in London, creating complex digital products that lead to better user experiences. I love to design beautifully simple interfaces, code, iterate and create. I am an experienced and capable Digital Product Designer with over two years' professional experience.

EXPERIENCE

Product Designer

CrowdScores · September 2015 - January 2017

CrowdScores is a real-time sports data application. I had the pleasure of working as the principal designer, taking responsibility for a variety of roles. Responsibilities included improving the existing product, researching and developing new features, conceptualising ideas and prototyping.

Product & Web Development

Suggestv · January 2017 - April 2017

Suggesty is the inventor of semantic video distribution. I was responsible for designing and facilitating the production of a semantic video distribution platform using React.

Freelance Designer

Prediction labs · January 2017 - Present

Numilli app - Bitcoin safe and easy. Numilli aims to makes it easy to securely buy and sell bitcoin currency on the go using a mobile app and ATM machine. My ongoing responsibility is the design and branding for the mobile app, web platform and ATM machines

Freelance Designer

Foreminds · March 2017 - Present

BaseSight - workforce management platform, which aims to help improve efficiency and productivity. Responsibilities included aiding in the development of the initial concept by generating wireframes and initial interface designs

EDUCATION

The University of Edinburgh · 2011 - 2015 Product design - 2:1 BA (Hons)

DESIGN SKILLS

Sketching UI/UX Design Interaction Design Prototyping Grid & Layout Design Research

DESIGN TOOLS



Sketch



Craft



Illustrator

Photoshop

Invision



Pixate

DEVELOPMENT



HTML

Javascript



CSS

CONTACT

iciclitira.com



07847395121